Let's talk about swing trading.
Which are the stocks
where you have to keep an eye on?  The
first name here is Oracle.
Sir, what swing trading strategy should be
adopted here?  What is your view?
Oracle
Oracle Financial Services Dude, you
asked me about swing trading, so let me open the
daily chart.
Retail participation in Aldo Oracle is low.  A ₹10,000
share is currently trading around ₹8,000 here.   There will be
an upside journey only if there is a weak daily closing above ₹8,000.
Ok.  Here, for swing trading,
you can consider these targets and proceed further.  The
next counter is that of Emphasis.
What swing trading strategy should be followed here sir?
Running at 2842.  Up around 2% today
inside swing trading strategy emphasis.
Swing Trade Inside Emphasis
If you want to take swing trade inside Emphasis, then it is
currently running at 2834.  Running at 2839.
A closing above 2850 above 2870 will
definitely give you an upside journey up to 3000.
Ok.  Upside Journey to 3000 is
coming here in the making inside Emphasis.   The
next counter is Kera Bank.
Running at 155.  Up 2.59%
and almost near its high
around 159.
What is the swing trading strategy being created in your bank according to you
?
We had discussed Can Bank two days ago also.
A good rally
is continuing and will continue.  In C Bank,
closing above 155 will give you comfortable targets of 165 as was told to you last
time also. Closing above 155 will definitely give
you targets of 165.
Ok?  So sir has said this target after a lot of push.
So I am very sure
that you should consider it very much and
keep it as it is.
Sir, what is your view regarding Varun Beverages here?
What swing trading strategy should be put here?   It is
trading at 484 and is up 1.5% today.
What are the targets being made within this?
Varun Beverages I do
n't know, I have not had Coke for a long time,
so this is also a problem, let me see,
Varun Beverages is doing well, it is coming up from the low,
if it closes above 490, you will
definitely get to see targets up to 520, I
mean last time also it was said
around 500, right now the
levels are 490 for swing trade, but roughly there is a resistance of 500,
closing above 500,
you can easily see its targets of 520.
Ok.  The next counter is
on SSI Prudential Life Insurance.
Running at 651.  0.60%
which is here today it is above.  What
swing trading strategy should be adopted here according to you
?
ICI Personal Life Insurance Company
closing above 660 is definitely going to give you a
target of 680 in it.
Ok.  A question has come up here regarding Eternal.
His name is RK Trader.
They are asking, Sir, please tell me about Eternal.  How do
you feel about what lies ahead
?  Eternal is running at 282.   I had just
spoken about Eternal.
We need a closing above 300.  If you get closing above 300 then it is
definitely going to
give you an upside.  The company has been
receiving support from a long-standing position.
Ok.  Sir, please look at SGVA also.
A question has come here from Indrajit ji.
It is saying that SjVA is a buy at 80.40.
What should be done?  If we
look at it now, it is running at 72.  Up 1%
today.
We have discussed this here in SBA before also.  I had
said it earlier also when it was running at
almost 80, when it was running around 80,
around 81, even then I had
said it with great emphasis that
lower targets are going to be hit in this and that is what is happening.  If it
breaks the level of 72, you will
easily see targets of 60 below.
You will see trading within 60.
So at 80 we were saying that
buying is not possible at all.  Rejection is going to come on 8084 also.
Avoid it at all costs
and if you have the time, take the
opportunity to exit.
Ok.  What is there here is a rhythm
by Shukla.  They are asking what should we do
in Eternal now?
Is it a good time to buy it?
Definitely a buying formation is forming.
But the confidence that the upside rally will be
found above 300.  But 280 levels is also
good.  I am continuously taking support from here.
Above 300 you will easily get the first target of 350.
Ok.  Here is a question from Vimal Singh ji.
What is being said here is that Sir,
long term investment has to be made in Indian Hotels and CG Power.  Can I
buy fresh food
here?
If we look at Indian Hotels right now, it is
running at 655.  Up 0.20%.  What
should be done here?  Is any buying formation forming
here?  Indian Hotels
ji, they have a long term view for
investment for the
long term. If we look at Indian Hotels, then it is
looking very weak in the charts
and last time also it was discussed that
till Indian Hotels did
not get a closing above 800, even then it was
told to avoid it,
only the closing above 800
was giving an upside target in it, last time it was said
that targets below 700 will show you further
downside, so 650 is going on, we will update it again today.
Closing below 650 will give
you a target of 600.
So it has to be completely avoided and I had
told you to avoid it earlier also.